Guide to the Francis V. Keesling Papers, 1908-1972 (inclusive), 1947-1972 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- U.S. Government Printing Office.
  - Report of the Task Force on the Structure of the Selective Service System.
  - October 16, 1967, (2 copies).
- _____
  - Report of the President's Commission on an All-Volunteer Armed Force. February 1970.
- _____.
  - Annual Report of the Director of Selective Service-- 1967. January 3, 1968.
- _____.
  - Selective Service as the Tide of the War Turns: The 3rd Report of the Director of the Selective Services.
  - 1943-1944.
- _____.
  - Selective Service in Wartime: Second Report of the Director of Selective Service.
  - 1941-42.
- _____.
  - Selective Service and Victory: The 4th Report of the Director of Selective Service.
  - 1944-45(published 1948).
- _____.
  - Selective Service in Peacetime: First report of the Director of Selective Service.
  - 1940-41.
- _____.
  - Report of the Director of the Office of Selective Service Records.
  - 1947-48.(published 1950).
- _____.
  - Selective Service Under the 1948 Act.
  - June 24, 1948--July 9, 1950.
  - U.S. Govt. Ptg. Office, 1951.
- _____.
  - Selective Service Under the 1948 Act Extended.
  - July 9, 1950--June 19, 1951.
  - U.S. Govt. Ptg. Office, 1953.
- _____.
  Headquarters Sixth U.S. Army.
  Martial Law Plan for Civil Defense.
  San Francisco Bay Complex.
  Presidio of S.F., CA
  November 1962.
- _____.
  - National Security Training System.
  - 20th Century Minutemen.
  - A Report to the President on a Reserve Forces Training Program.
- _____.
  - Selective Service System, Statistical Section.
  - Calls and Inductions.
  - by State and Branch of Service.
  - November 1970.
- _____.
  - Selective Service System.
  - State Director's Conference.
  - 1967.
- _____.
  - Selective Service System.
  - Background of Selective Service.
  - Manual #1, September 1947.
- _____.
  - Statement of Lt. Gen. Lewis B. Hershey, Director of the Selective Service before the Committee on Armed Services, House of Representatives.
  - May 10, 1967.
- _____.
  - Forms and Information for the Local Draft Boards of California.
- _____.
  - House of Representatives.
  - Hearings before the Committee on Armed Services.
    - 1) Amending & Extending the Draft Law and Related Authorities. 1967.
    - 2) Extension of the Military Training and Service Act. 1967.
- _____.
  - U.S. Sentate.
  - Hearings before the Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations. 1953.
- _____.
  - House of Representatives.
  - Hearings before the Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations. 1949.
- _____.
  - U.S. Senate.
  - Hearings before a Subcommittee of the Committee of Public Works. 1949.
- _____.
  - Miscellaneous Reports to the Senate and House of Representatives.
- _____.
  - The Congressional Record.
  - Miscellaneous issues: 1950, 1953.
- _____.
  - Army Digest.
  - November 1966.
ST: dar
8/3/79